Either we're Americans fighting on
behalf of America and American ideals or
we're not. We're Israeli puppets and I'm
unwilling to be an Israeli stooge.
>> permanent intelligence sharing with
Israel and ties it to their qualitative
military edge and restricts future
presidents from scaling it back.
>> between the United States and Israel
that would literally join
the US and Israel at the hip in terms of
technical technological cooperation.
Israel is ranked in the intelligence
community as critical threat for
counterintelligence. And instead, the
response now is
ah, just give them everything anyway.
Just give it [music] to them.
The entire US intelligence community,
not just the CIA, but all 18 members of
the US intelligence community
wrote two
national intelligence estimates.
Both concluding unanimously
that the Iranians did not have a nuclear
weapons program.
Besides that, in 2003, Ayatollah
Khamenei, the the late Ayatollah
Khamenei,
um issued a fatwa in 2003 declaring it a
sin
to develop a nuclear weapon. There was
no Iranian nuclear weapon or nuclear
weapons program, period. But that
narrative didn't serve of Israeli
interests.
And so Benjamin Netanyahu just kept
doing what he's always done and what
Israeli prime ministers before him have
done. They've come to the White House,
usually several times a year, and
they've said, "Bomb Iran. Bomb Iran.
Bomb Iran." And every single president
said no until this one.
The Israelis convinced, apparently,
Donald Trump that the Iranian government
was a house of cards
and that as soon as the first missiles
began flying
uh [clears throat] the whole thing would
just collapse.
Well, anybody
who knows anything about Iran knew that
that wasn't true. Even if you don't know
anything about Iran, if you just
followed the Iraq war in 2003, you knew
that that wasn't true. We are never seen
as liberators.
We're always seen as invaders and
occupiers.
The Israelis even more so.
And so there was never any chance that
this Iranian government was going to
fall. And look at it this way, too. Iran
is the size of Western Europe, the
entire
landmass of Western Europe. It's 3.8
times the size of Iraq
and it has a forbidding topography.
You can't just bomb Iran think it's
going to fall apart and then your
handpicked stooge comes in and just
takes over and everybody lives happily
ever after.
That's a fantasy. It was never ever
going to happen.
But this president thought that it
would. It's It's deeper than just Donald
Trump. I'm not blaming Donald Trump.
I'm blaming the entire US government.
Just
in the last 48 hours
a Republican congressman from
Pennsylvania and a Republican
congressman from Ohio sponsored a bill
in the House of Representatives to give
US veteran veterans benefits
to any American who joins the IDF.
That is a [__] outrage.
As an American, I consider that to be
treason. If you If you're If you're
fighting on behalf of a foreign military
you shouldn't be an American citizen.
Period. We have members of Congress like
this this
fine of Florida who show up on the floor
of the House of Representatives wearing
an IDF uniform.
We have members of the US Senate
including the chairman of the Senate
Intelligence Committee, Tom Cotton,
who have Israeli flags outside their
offices on Capitol Hill.
What is that?
Either we're Americans fighting on
behalf of America and American ideals or
we're not. We're Israeli puppets and
stooges and I'm unwilling to be an
Israeli stooge.
>> Well, you mentioned it sort of you sort
of touched on it. Some of the
legislation that's going through our
government if you could call it that
right now. Um, I want to start with two
pieces of that. You mentioned I can't
remember that the number to that one.
It's like 8222 or something for the one
about the veterans benefits which is
shocking and evil.
>> something.
>> Yeah, yeah, that's my bad. Yeah. Well, I
want to talk about 224 of FY 27 NDAA
which creates a permanent DOD DOD
executive agent for the US military
fusion or US Israeli military fusion as
well as section 2 622 and this would be
your wheelhouse section 622 of the
intelligence authorization act for 2027
slipped in by Tom Cotton
does the same thing on the intelligence
side. It locks in permanent intelligence
sharing with Israel and ties it to their
qualitative military edge and restricts
future presidents from scaling it back.
What is going on? Let's start with the
military merger in the NDAA and then I
want you to give us your intel expertise
on the intel side.
>> You know, and isn't it ironic
that this same week that this is
happening, what you just said,
what we're also seeing is the Defense
Intelligence Agency had to issue a
warning to its own employees
about stepped up Israeli spying on the
United States.
>> Mhm.
>> And and people just look at you square
in the eye here in Washington like,
there's no there's no problem here. So,
the NDAA, the National Defense
Authorization Act of 2027, you know,
NDAAs just by their nature are just
rotten, evil, terrible pieces of
legislation. They usually run between
1,500 and 3,000 pages. Nobody reads
them. And members of Congress like Tom
Cotton and Lindsey Graham and Ted Cruz
can slip in anything they want. They get
themselves appointed to the to the
conference committee so they can ensure
that in the clean bill that comes out at
the end of the negotiation, their
provisions are still inside. It's a it's
a filthy business.
>> Mhm.
>> So, the NDAA for 2027 as proposed would
create an unprecedented liaison
relationship at the Pentagon between the
United States and Israel that would
literally join
the US and Israel at the hip in terms of
technical technological cooperation.
And let me back up with with a uh
with an example that I use quite
frequently. When we were developing the
F-35, the the state-of-the-art, most
sophisticated, blah blah blah fighter
jet,
which nobody likes.
Um the F-35, the Israelis were the first
ones to come to us and they said, we
want this new F-35. And we said, okay,
we'll give it to you first. We're going
to call it the F-35I for Israel and
we're going to degrade the avionics just
barely just in case, God forbid, one of
them gets shot down and the Russians or
the Chinese get it, they're not going to
have our our top most secrets. The
Israelis said, nope, not good enough. We
want the F-35
as is, as you have it. We want the same
one you have.
In the meantime, at the same time,
the Emiratis came to us and they said,
we want this F-35.
And we said okay, we'll sell it to you.
We're going to call it the F-35 e for
Emirates.
And we're going to degrade the avionics
just a little bit so God forbid if, you
know, you're in a dog fight over Iran
and one gets shot down that the that the
Chinese or the Russians don't get it.
They said fine, we'll take it.
The Israelis
sent out hundreds of spies
all across America
and our defense contractors to steal
that 2% of the avionics that we wouldn't
give them.
Well, with the National Defense
Authorization Act of 2027, they don't
need the spies to steal it cuz we're
just going to fork it over.
Just hand it over to them. Here you go.
Here are our most sensitive secrets.
Now, Israel is the same country
that sold our talks top secret
information to the Soviet Union
through John that they that they
acquired through Jonathan Pollard in
order to bring a plane load of Russian
Jews into Israel.
Um and that's okay. We just have chosen
not to pay attention to that. We've
chosen not to pay attention to the new
DIA announcement that the Israelis have
stepped up their espionage against the
US government.
And we're just pretending that all is is
perfectly fine in the land of milk and
honey and we're going to give the
Israelis anything that they want. And as
an American, I'm appalled by this.
Appalled.
>> It's sick.
>> We have to We have to call it like it
is. I think also that there is, if you
look at it, the close coordination was
also revealed during the genocide in
Gaza. You remember that famous photo
that Biden was visiting Israel and there
were some special operators there. Then
they tried to take down the photo
fast enough to try to say that there
were no Americans there, special
operators, but clearly Max Blumenthal
and others were reposting it.
>> Yes. there it was, American troops with
our patches and everything, American
flags, and there they were being greeted
by President Biden in Israel.
>> Mhm. After we said repeatedly
that we did not have a military prison
presence there.
>> We do.
>> Yes, we do.
>> Well, what about section 22622,
which ties the intelligence sides
together? What is the what do they mean
by Israel's qualitative military edge
and this sort of insertion of this
permanent
locking in between the two intelligence
agencies? You've talked in previous
interviews extensively about the Mossad
infiltrating all sorts of agencies in
the United States. And now I think
you're alluding to the fact that this
makes that unnecessary.
>> Yeah, it does. It makes it unnecessary.
Israel is ranked in the intelligence
community as critical threat for
counterintelligence. Do you know the
other countries that are ranked for
critical in threat?
>> North Korea.
>> Yeah, North Korea, China, Russia, Iran,
and Cuba.
And Israel.
Critical threat to the United States
government.
And this is specifically for spying
against the US government and
infiltrating the US government. Critical
threat.
And instead, the response now is
eh, just give them everything anyway.
Just give it to them.
>> Yeah, I jokingly said you you mitigate
the threat by becoming it.
>> Yeah.
>> [laughter]
>> That's exactly right. How sick is that?
>> [music]